

SHAUN SEIDMAN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT



shaunseidman@gmail.com



(949)599-4271



shaunseidman.com



1600 Glenarm Pl #806, Denver, CO 80202

ABOUT

Thanks for taking a look. I am a full stack developer with a passion for creating, problem solving and continuing to learn and grow. My previous experience in managing a small business and team building have helped to solidify my work techniques with others and also instill a never-quit attitude.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML
- Vue.Js
- React
- Swift
- Git
- Agile
- Cypress

- Knex
- Python
- PostgreSQL
- Express
- Agile
- Node.Js
- SASS

PROJECTS

shaunseidman.com

A work in progress personal website made with Vue.JS

Pay It Forward

An iOS app that makes donating easier. Local institutions are able to create a profile and upload items needed for donation. The user is then able to view the organizations and then view the posted items. A Realm database holds the data for both the organization as well as the items and executes the CRUD functionality to alert when an item has been completed or submitted.

Fridge Vision

A collaborative group project implementing React Native, Clarafi image recognition and Amazon Web Services S3 image hosting.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Proper Barbershop - General Manager - March 2016 - November 2017

As the GM I created accounts with wholesale men's grooming products to carry in store. As well as managing inventory and the 15 barbers, I was in charge of accounts payable and helped open a second location.

Novo Coffee - Store Manager - February 2015 - March 2016

Manage the cafe as well as place order and make the weekly schedule for 7 employees

Native Foods - Assistant Store Manager November 2014 - February 2015

Created schedule for both front and back of house employees.
Assisted and served customers as well worked back of house shifts when need be

ZMediaNow LLC- Customer Service Manager February 2013 - October 2014

I worked with payments, refunds, identity verification, changing payments methods, doing verifications on our clients' profiles, handling with private information, approving, banning and helping customers to be approved on their profiles, removing stolen internet's content from our websites, attending Skype meetings and always updating myself on technology to make our customer's life easier

EDUCATION

Galvanize Web Development Immersive

November 2017 - May 2018

Orange Coast College

June 2009 - December 2011

Sonoma State University

August 2008 - June 2009